

Manay Madaan

Senior Product Designer

INTRODUCTION

A designer & research enthusiast with over 9 Years of cross-industry experience creating exceptional UX across domains & devices for both B2B and B2C businesses.

My current expertise lays in domains like Fintech, SAAS, Hospitality & Restaurant-Tech, entertainment and prop-Tech

CONTACT



PORTFOLIO

https://linktr.ee/uxandmore



EMAIL

yomana.madaan@gmail.com



PHONE

(+91) 9716588728

SOCIALS



LINKEDIN
@helllomanav



YOUTUBE @uxandmore



INSTAGRAM
@uxandmore

"Good design is invisible "

EXPERIENCE

AlgoTest (YC S22) · Founding Principal Designer - Contract

JUN 2023 - MAY 2024

- Increased the signup rate from 15% to 20% by redesigning the Homepage, sign-up form and building product marketing and landing pages.
- · Built 2 new products units with a 30% and 10% revenue contribution respectively.
- · Bumped revenue by 1% by addressing minor design improvements over 3 months.
- · Evangelised & Led GTM & marketing design.
- · Introduced Design-Engineering-Product handoff and QA processes.
- · Conducted research to identify personas, new product areas and improve user journeys.

Tickertape (Smallcase) · Senior Product Designer

MAY 2022 - MAR 2023

- · Led the pod of four designers responsible for:
 - · Stocks, Mutual Funds, Indices & ETF page
 - · Equity and Mutual fund Portfolio
 - · Smallcase pages and transactions
 - · Stock & Mutual Fund Screener
 - · Watchlist and Basket
- Established a structured design critique (Design Jams) improving cross-pod collaboration, early feedback and to minimise design debt.
- · Produced in-house video series called "Figma for developers" that improved handoff, collaboration and and efficiency within the design and engineering team.

Scripbox · Senior Product Designer

IUL 2021 - APR 2022

- · Collaborated with founders along with product managers in building an exceptional retirement planner
- · Redesigned the profile section for mobile and desktop web.

Housing · Designer & Researcher

FEB 2019 - JUL 2021

- Redesigned the Property detail pages in 9 months increasing conversion by 5%, moving the SEO ranking by a few spots and engagement by 5%.
- \cdot Worked on various growth & experimental features to increases overall user engagement by 7%.
- Performed research for Landmark based search, product detail pages, Broker partner app, price trends and neighbourhood search.

TechGig · UX Designer

SEP 2017 - FEB 2019

- Redesigned the Hackathon & Coding Challenge form that reduced the creation timer from 20 minutes to 5 minutes.
- · Scaled new design system from one page to across product in 6 months.
- · Evangelised and performed UX research for new products and initiatives

BookMyShow · Product designer

MAY 2017 - SEP 2017

· Contributed building the Information Architecture for the profile section of BookMyShow android and mobile web app.

Almond Solutions Pvt. Ltd · Founding UX Designer

SEP 2015 - MAR 2017

- Collaborated with the founder and engineers in building B2B and B2C products for restaurant and diner respectively.
- \cdot Built products like Table, digital menu, inventory, guest and waitlist management and POS systems.

EDUCATION

Delhi Institute of Technology & Management

B.Tech - Computer Science Engineering

SEP 2012 - JUL 2016

Mount Abu Public School (New Delhi)

CBSE 12 Boards - Science + Computers

APR 2010 - JUL 2012